http://www.wildernessfamilynaturals.com/pages/privacy-policy

Wildly Organic Rewards
Welcome from Pinterest! You've just activated a 20% discount code + free shipping!Use code: PINTEREST20 at checkout. *Retail only, free shipping to contiguous U.S., limit 1 use per customer.
Welcome from Pinterest! You've just activated a 20% discount code + free shipping! Use code: PINTEREST20 at checkout. *Retail only, free shipping to contiguous U.S., limit 1 use per customer.
Welcome from Instagram! You've just activated a 15% discount code + free shipping!Use code: INSTAGRAM at checkout. *Retail only, nuts collection excluded, limit 1 use per customer.
Welcome from Instagram! You've just activated a 15% discount code + free shipping! Use code: INSTAGRAM at checkout. *Retail only, nuts collection excluded, limit 1 use per customer.
Introduction
We at Wildly Organic are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.
Wildly Organic has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address, phone number, or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Wildly Organic Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Web, we may transfer that Information within Wildly Organic but it will not be transferred beyond this company other than to third party service providers.
Wildly Organic strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy.  Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Wildly Organic intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies.  A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about website activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user.  Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the website. Removing cookies will also remove all items from your cart and may break website functionality during a sale or otherwise.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your Web experience.  We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
Security
Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Wildly Organic or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.
Access/Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Wildly Organic wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Wildly Organic should you need to update or correct that Information.  If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to Wildly Organic and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
Third Party Services
Third parties provide certain services available on wildlyorganic.com on Wildly Organic's behalf.  Wildly Organic may provide information, including Personal Information, that Wildly Organic collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Wildly Organic maintains its website and mailing lists.  Wildly Organic will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Wildly Organic's behalf.
Wildly Organic does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Wildly Organic's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.  Similarly, it is against Wildly Organic's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.
Your Consent
By using this website, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Wildly Organic's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Wildly Organic collects Personal Information on the Web.  Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our website for a reasonable period of time.
Shop Our Products
Cacao & Cacao Products
Bulk Coconut Oil
Coconut Oil
Coconut Products
Nuts & Seeds
Dried Fruits
Flours
Natural Sweeteners
Cooking Oils
Popcorn Products
Rice & Grains
Subscribe
Join our mailing list to geta 10% discount via email!
Browse Our Recipes
Chocolate
Dairy-Free
Desserts
Gluten-Free
Keto
Main Dishes
Paleo
Affiliate Program
*Free and flat-rate shipping options apply to retail customers in the lower 48 states, continental U.S. only. We do not refund shipping charges once an order has shipped.
Allergen Warning: Our products are packaged and processed in a facility that also processes tree nuts (never peanuts) and other allergens.
©2020 Wildly Organic | All Rights Reserved
+1 (218) 226-3985
help@wildlyorganic.com
These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.
Amazon
American Express
Apple Pay
Discover
Mastercard
PayPal
Visa
Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Return Policy | Sitemap
Free shipping for all orders of $49+ within the Contiguous U.S.
Added to your cart:
Cart Subtotal
close
